{
    "subject": "resource/James_Tien_(politician)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "James Tien Pei-chun",
    "human_readable": "The name of James Tien (politician) is James Tien Pei-chun.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8919884562492371,
            "question": "What is the full name of James Tien?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8232710957527161,
            "question": "How is James Tien known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7974762320518494,
            "question": "What is James Tien's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7554255723953247,
            "question": "What is the significance of James Tien in Hong Kong politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.710944652557373,
            "question": "What political parties has James Tien been affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6353799104690552,
            "question": "What are some notable achievements of James Tien?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5024974942207336,
            "question": "Who are some influential people in James Tien's life or career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.461479127407074,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by James Tien in his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4468318223953247,
            "question": "How has James Tien influenced public opinion on political issues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4407975375652313,
            "question": "What are some key policies advocated by James Tien?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of James Tien (politician) is James Tien Pei-chun.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7889_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has James Tien influenced public opinion on political issues?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7889_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some challenges faced by James Tien in his career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7889_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some influential people in James Tien's life or career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7889_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7889_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain two entries for a person named James Tien, one with the birthdate January 8, 1947 (James Tien Pei-chun), and another with the birthdate May 28, 1942 (James Tien-chun). The first entry is about a politician, while the others are about an actor. Therefore, the statement \"The name of James Tien (politician) is James Tien Pei-chun\" is not supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about a person named James Tien Pei-chun, GBS, OBE, JP, which matches the name \"James Tien (politician)\" in the query. Therefore, the statement that his full name is James Tien Pei-chun is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The provided context information includes a statement \"For other people with the same name, see James Tien (disambiguation).\" which implies that there are multiple individuals with the name James Tien, and then it specifically mentions \"James Tien Pei-chun\" as one of them.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}